Guide to the New York City Tavern License Collection 1783-1797, 1862 MS 443.28
New-York Historical Society
- 409. Seventh Ward. John Whippo (Innholder), 1797 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- License ?. Dock Ward. Silvannus Seely, 1784 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dated 1784 Januray 3
- License ?. Ward ?. John McPherson (Innholder), 1789 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dated 1789 May 6
- 219. Out Ward. Frederick Shuber (Grocer), 1790 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dated 1790 March 8
- 101. Out Ward. Joshua Meals (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 102. Dock Ward. Bernard Rapalse (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 106. Montgomery Ward. William Ervin (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 107. West Ward. George Allison (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 108. North Ward. Mary Murphy (Widow), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 109. Montgomery Ward. William Geach (Yeoman), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 110. South Ward. John Leighton (Inholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 111. East Ward. Bernard Byrne (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 112. South Ward. Jacob Hutchins (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 113. North Ward. John Colwell (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 114. Montgomery Ward. Joseph Towers (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 115. Out Ward. Frederick Shuber (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 116. West Ward. Daniel Parcutt (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 117. Dock Ward. Bernard Cleodon (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 119. East Ward. William Golden (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 120. North Ward. John Martin (Yeoman), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 121. South Ward. Theodorus J. Hamilton (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 122. South Ward. Lewis Claphorne (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 123. East Ward. Jacob Wilkins (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 124. Out Ward. Catherine Wisar (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 125. Out Ward. Gerard Hardenbrook (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 127. South Ward. George Hall (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 129. Montgomery Ward. John Rankin (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 130. Out Ward. Susanna Day (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 131. West Ward. Joseph Corre (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 132. South Ward. Abraham Bond (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 133. South Ward. Charles McLean (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 134. South Ward. Jacob Crocheron (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 135. Montgomery Ward. Henry Holiday (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 136. South Ward. Susanna Sherer (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 137. West Ward. William Harris (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 138. West Ward. Peter Deschent (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 139. East Ward. Jacob Concklin (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 140. Montgomery Ward. Sarah Everit (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 141. Montgomery Ward. Thomas Whitelaw (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 143. North Ward. John Carrow (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 144. Out Ward. Jacob Hauptman (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 145. West Ward. Joseph Stanton (Lumber Merchant), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 146. East Ward. Elizabeth Dolbey (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 148. East Ward. Christopher Berkley (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 149. East Ward. Timothy Crawley (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 150. North Ward. Andrew Lee (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 266. West Ward. James Ayman (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 267. Montgomery Ward. John McPherson (Mariner), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 268. North Ward. John Currie (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 269. West Ward. Abraham Archer (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 270. East Ward. John Everit (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 271. Out Ward. Edward Collins (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 273. West Ward. John Grantzeback (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 274. Out Ward. Abraham Cannon (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 275. East Ward. Peter A. Schenk (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dated 1791 March 8
- 276. Montgomery Ward. John Gamson (Mariner), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 277. Montgomery Ward. James Savage (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 278. West Ward. James Leonard (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 279. Out Ward. John C. Graham (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 280. East Ward. William Bradford (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 282. North Ward. Dorothy Johnson (Widow), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 283. Montgomery Ward. Anthony Simmons (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 284. Montgomery Ward. James Pryor (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 285. South Ward. John Walher (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 286. North Ward. John Mildenberger (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dated 1791 March 9
- 287. West Ward. John Bonsall (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 289. East Ward. Catherine Bradford (Gentlewoman), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 290. East Ward. Samuel Carman (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 291. North Ward. Mary English (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 293. Out Ward. Richard Varian (Butcher), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 294. East Ward. George Garland, Jr. (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 295. East Ward. John Mulholland (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dated 1791 March 9. John Mulholland of the Dock Ward.
- 296. West Ward. Benjamin Waldron (Innholder), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 297. Out Ward. Adam Fink (Butcher), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 299. West Ward. Samuel Walker (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 300. Montgomery Ward. John Cross (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 301. North Ward. Phillip Becannon (Sugar Baker), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 302. South Ward. James Richardson (Mariner), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Dated 1791 March 11
- 303. East Ward. John Swan (Grocer), 1791 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 16. Ward ?. Thomas Townsend (Grocer), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 March 1
- 404. Seventh Ward. Ann Johnston (Widow), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 8
- 405. Second Ward. Francis Filner (Yeoman), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 406. Fifth Ward. James Butler (Sail Maker), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 407. Second Ward. Murdoch McLean (Yeoman), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 408. First Ward. James FitzPatrick (Carpenter), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 409. Seventh Ward. William Lumbert (Yeoman), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 9
- 410. Seventh Ward. Abigail Spicer (Widow), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 10
- 411. First Ward. John Simmons (Coach Maker), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 412. Fifth Ward. Daniel Gantley (Cordswainer), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 413. Second Ward. Thomas Nuntley (Innholder), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 11
- 414. Second Ward. Jacob Mott (Grocer), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 415. Second Ward. Platt Smith (Grocer), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 416. Fifth Ward. James King (Yeoman), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 12
- 417. First Ward. William Arnold (Rope Maker), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 418. Sixth Ward. William Chevers (Tailor), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 14
- 419. Fifth Ward. John Carrow (Constable), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 15
- 420. Seventh Ward. William Battells (Grocer), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 421. First Ward. John Fowler (Innholder), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 16
- 422. Seventh Ward. James Grierson (Innholder), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 17
- 423. First Ward. John Vrinnik (?)(Yeoman), 1792 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1792 May 18
- 97. First Ward. Anthony Clawson (Cartman), 1793 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1793 March 1
- 331. Fourth Ward. Hendrick Meyers (Grocer), 1793 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1793 March 5
- 568. Fourth Ward. Andre Mathieu (Yeoman), 1794 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1794 September 25
- 577. Sixth Ward. John Wench (Grocer), 1794 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1794 November 10
- 401. First Ward. John McGuire (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 402. Sixth Ward. Peter Barr (Weaver), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 403. Second Ward. William Miller (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 404. Sixth Ward. William Robertson (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 405. Fifth Ward. Alexander Cowley (Rigger), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 406. First Ward. Vincent Dill (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 409. Fifth Ward. John Carrow (Marshall), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 410. Seventh Ward. Samuel B. Waldron (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 411. Fifth Ward. Laurence Byrne (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 412. Fifth Ward. William Brown (Yeoman), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 413. Sixth Ward. Archibald Nesbit (Carpenter), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 414. Sixth Ward. John Joise (Yeoman), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 415. Seventh Ward. Abraham Van Ansdalen (Carpenter), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 416. Seventh Ward. Isaac Lopes (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 417. Seventh Ward. Henry Raymond (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 419. Seventh Ward. David Wilson (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 420. Seventh Ward. Samuel Burdges (Carpenter), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 421. Sixth Ward. Israel Anderson (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 422. Seventh Ward. Gilbert Knapp (Butcher), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 423. First Ward. John Tuttle (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 424. Fifth Ward. Thomas Ellis (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 425. Seventh Ward. John Bennet (Baker), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 426. Fourth Ward. Erasmus Lewis; John Fine (Grocers), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 427. Fourth Ward. Daniel Trembly; David Demarest (Grocers), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 428. Seventh Ward. John Hoster (Yeoman), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 429. Sixth Ward. Peter Angevione (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 431. Fourth Ward. Uzel Bradwell (Carpenter), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 433. Fourth Ward. George Adamson (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 434. Fourth Ward. Joseph Smith, Jr. (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 435. Seventh Ward. Richard Jacques (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 436. First Ward. Thomas Lovell (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 437. Seventh Ward. James Sowerby (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 438. Fifth Ward. Sarah Hunt (Widow), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 439. First Ward. George Wallgrove (Cooper), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 440. Sixth Ward. Oliver Jacques (Cartman), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 442. First Ward. John Hillyer (Cooper), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 445. Third Ward. Benjamin Bennet & Beza E. Bliss (Grocers), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 446. Fifth Ward. John Cameron (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 447. Fifth Ward. Sally Rawson (Widow), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 448. Fifth Ward. Thomas Jaffray (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 449. Second Ward. Elizabeth Baker (Widow), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 450. Third Ward. Charles Gardner (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 451. Fifth Ward. Robert Smith (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 452. Fourth Ward. Joseph Pettit (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 453. First Ward. James Glass (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 454. Third Ward. James Miller (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 455. Seventh Ward. Jacob Tier (Butcher), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 456. Fifth Ward. Mary Finlay (Widow), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 458. First Ward. William Carson (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Dated 1796 March 7
- 459. Sixth Ward. Daniel Ruckel (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 460. Sixth Ward. William Harrison (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 461. Seventh Ward. John Dietz (Constable), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 462. First Ward. John C. Graham (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 463. Sixth Ward. Jacob Evans (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 464. Second Ward. Ebenezer Briggs (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 465. Seventh Ward. Henry Donn Trip (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 466. Second Ward. Abraham Valentine (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 468. Sixth Ward. Joseph Watkins (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 469. Sixth Ward. William Martine (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 470. Seventh Ward. Matt Smith (Shipwright), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 471. Fifth Ward. James Black (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 472. Fifth Ward. James Pryor (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 473. Seventh Ward. John Richman (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 474. Seventh Ward. John Stevenson (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 475. Seventh Ward. George Gray, Jr. (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 478. Seventh Ward. Robert McGowan (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 479. Fifth Ward. Mary Reid (Widow), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 481. First Ward. Robert Rattoone (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 482. First Ward. William Hillyer (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 483. Fifth Ward. Daniel Mack (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 484. Fourth Ward. Morris Smith (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 485. Seventh Ward. Daniel Tier (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 486. Fourth Ward. Ann Woodage (Widow), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 488. Third Ward. Michael Keenan (Innholder), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 489. Seventh Ward. James Baker (Mason), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 490. Fourth Ward. Samuel Clark (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 491. Fifth Ward. Mary McDonald (Widow), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 492. Fifth Ward. Neil McLaren (Yeoman), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 593 (miswritten 493). Seventh Ward. Patrick McFarlin (Yeoman), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 494. Seventh Ward. John Vreeland (Grocer), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 495. Fifth Ward. John Walker (Boatman), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 496. Fifth Ward. Seth R. Kneeland (Carpenter), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 497. Seventh Ward. John Beck (Ship Chandler), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 498. Second Ward. Mayaca Van Horne (Widow), 1796 (Box 1, Folder 6)